<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Not My Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Not My Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.143.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 21:52:51 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Just a Sunday</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/just-a-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 21:52:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/just-a-sunday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, as the name says, it&amp;rsquo;s just another Sunday, doing what I always do. But today, I did some case studies about transmission lines since I have to submit a report tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I watched some YouTube videos sent by my teacher and browsed Google for more information on the topic. After completing that, I opened the &lt;strong&gt;Spider-Man&lt;/strong&gt; game and played for like 3 or 4 hours. That game is really fun, though!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Another Day</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/just-another-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 21:40:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/just-another-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just another day, as the name says—I spent this day doing nothing (did something but not much).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I woke up at &lt;strong&gt;5 AM&lt;/strong&gt;, checked my mails, scrolled for some time, and watched &lt;strong&gt;two movies&lt;/strong&gt;. Time passed quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the movies, I took a little &lt;strong&gt;nap for an hour&lt;/strong&gt; and then remembered that I had installed &lt;em&gt;Spider-Man 2&lt;/em&gt; but hadn&amp;rsquo;t played it yet. So, I opened my laptop, started playing, and &lt;strong&gt;four hours&lt;/strong&gt; flew by.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Different Day</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/different-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 22:16:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/different-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-different-day&#34;&gt;A Different Day&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may think why I chose this name for this blog. Well, my brain is not braining, so I just named it whatever came to my mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morning-routine&#34;&gt;Morning Routine&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Woke up at 5 AM, then scrolled mindlessly on Instagram for like 45+ mins. After that, I started studying classwork.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I created a website yesterday, I wanted to change its theme. Initially, I tried the &lt;strong&gt;Coder&lt;/strong&gt; theme, but the content wasn’t visible, so I switched to &lt;strong&gt;PaperMod&lt;/strong&gt; instead. Changing the theme took some time. After some chatting with my friend, I left for college.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating This Website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-this-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:47:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/creating-this-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;1322025&#34;&gt;13/2/2025&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I created this website successfully with the help of my friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actually, I started working on creating this website yesterday, and I had already built it. But I couldn’t make the website look the same as it did on localhost. I sought help from ChatGPT, which helped me, but I still hadn’t solved the error. Then, my laptop’s battery was close to dead, so I turned it off and decided to continue tomorrow—which is today.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
